GUSTAVO H. MIGLIORINI

Data Scientist

Londrina, Paraná, Brazil +55 19 9 98095841 gustavomig@gmail.com https://gustavomigliorini.netlify.app/

SUMMARY:

Data Scientist with broad experience in scientific research and programming languages such as R, Python and SQL. A quick learner with the ability to solve problems independently, a critical thinker, and a proactive team player. Previous experience working as a Data Analyst in both corporate and academic environments.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

ALS Life Sciences

Data Analyst | February, 2022 - December, 2022

- · Analyses of clinical research data
- · Validation of statistical results
- Review of statistical reports

Federal University of Pernambuco

Research Data Analyst | May, 2021 - December, 2021

- · Analyses of research data
- Teaching of R programming and statistical analyses
- Design of research experiments
- · Scientific writing and publication

EDUCATION:

2021 - 2022 | Federal University of Technology - Paraná, Brazil

Data Science - Specialist

Capstone project: Identification of birds from Brazil through deep learning for image classification

2014 - 2018 | State University of São Paulo, Brazil

Environmental Sciences - PhD

SKILLS:

- Python
- R language
- SQL

- Power BI
- Machine Learning
- GitHub

CERTIFICATIONS:

- Databricks Lakehouse Fundamentals, Databricks
- · BigQuery for Data Analysis, Google
- · Python for Data Science, IBM
- Power BI, Udemy